- id: ckw-l38-6254
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - スペシャル
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6262
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - バナナ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6267
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - アレンジ
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6273
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - テント
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6276
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ライバル
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6281
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - コップ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6307
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - タウン
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6313
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ブラシ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6315
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - オブジェクト
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6315
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - バッテリー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6323
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ターン
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6326
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - パッケージ
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6331
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - アンテナ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6331
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - フィルター
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l38-6331
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - レイアウト
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []
